

## **ABOUT ME**

Santiago Ortiz Guevara, a 22 years old Colombian **Product Designer & Developer**, with interest and work experience in **Front-End Development** & **User Interface Design** (UI).

My creativity allows me to build experiences and interfaces, based on human feelings and needs.

# CONTACT

Bē behance.net/santiagortizgue

**Portfolio:** santiagortizgue.github.io

© @santiagortizgue

linkedin.com/in/santiago-ortiz-guevara/

**&** +57 3233838030

santiagortizgue@gmail.com

# **HOBBIES**

Photography

Online Learning





## **LEGAL DATA**

c.c.1144102996 - ID in Colombia

# **SANTIAGO**



Product Designer & Developer

### **EDUCATION**

Interactive Media Design
Universidad Icesi, Cali, Colombia



### **TALENT & SKILLS**

**Talents -** Problem Solving, Team Work, Creativity & Results Orientation. **Skills -** Front-End Development, UI Design, Prototyping & UX Design

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

**Company:** Universidad Icesi. **Position:** Programming Assistant **Immediate boss:** Jose Andrés Moncada. **Contact:** +57 5552334 ext. 8389. **Period:** 2 years (2017 - 2018).

**Company:** Angular Diseño + Interacción **Position:** Product Designer & Developer

Immediate boss: Diego Barbosa Contact: +57 3002895394 Period: +1 year (2020 - 2021).

Feriod: +1 year (2020 - 2021).

I currently work as **User Interface Designer** at **Ilógica**, since Feb 2021 **Immediate boss:** Estefanía Cotrini **Contact:** linkedin.com/in/estefaniacotrini

**Research Experience -** "Audio-tactile priming to guide information recall in edutainment", 2018.

**Software Experience -** Adobe Creative Suite, Figma, Visual Studio Code, Unity3D & Blender.

**Programming Experience -** JavaScript, TypeScript, Java, C#, HTML, CSS, SASS, NodeJS & Express, ReactJS, Redux, Firebase & SteamVR.

### **LANGUAGES**

**Spanish** - Native Language

**English, Intermediate** - Icesi University, The British Academy (Cali, Colombia).